var jsonData = {
data: [ {
		category: "Meitschi",
		data: [ { problem: "yugldxpRDMo?t=10",
				  solution: "gJLIiF15wjQ?t=50"},
  				{ problem: "HmQbk5Zlmdk?t=10",
			      solution: "IbV7Mzx6m5Y" },
				{ problem: "fXWkmwuOo30?t=15",
				  solution: "ff" },
				{ problem: "QKxYdAdmnJY?t=37",
				  solution: "ff" },
				{ problem: "wdclClo2oA8?t=21",
				  solution: "XYXczDB8VrY" }
			  ]
		},
		{
		category: "Buebe",
		data: [ { problem: "zY0--b6DLqQ",
			      solution: "zY0--b6DLqQ" },
  				{ problem: "XVCNtyZdGD0?t=17",
			      solution: "hTWKbfoikeg" },
				{ problem: "PEQxWg92Ux4",
				  solution: "3KL9mRus19o" },
				{ problem: "it2gZnA7xBY?t=93",
				  solution: "ryDOy3AosBw" },
				{ problem: "MSDFVcqrOMs?t=39",
				  solution: "Xu3FTEmN-eg?t=14" }
			  ]
		},
		{
		category: "Schwiizer Musig",
		data: [ { problem: "2wkekZpikbY",
			      solution: "2wkekZpikbY" },
  				{ problem: "vhOqeM4fyZA?t=13",
			      solution: "ff" },
				{ problem: "TeLK1iZdy1w?t=20",
				  solution: "Ckom3gf57Yw?t=15" },
				{ problem: "7_SAMrDnXOE?t=19",
				  solution: "ff" },
				{ problem: "s0-cMdewJpQ",
				  solution: "3mbBbFH9fAg?t=22"}
			  ]
		},
		{
		category: "No Gender",
		data: [ { problem: "m_HnBac5jWs?t=11",
				  solution: "ff" },
				{ problem: "uor4XLlZQkQ?t=10",
				  solution: "JYIaWeVL1JM" },
				{ problem: "GhgG5dEHQXM?t=17",
				  solution: "GhgG5dEHQXM?t=17" },
				{ problem: "G6-UlMs7Qxs?t=22",
				  solution: "VUosAGDM8Sg?t=17" },
				{ problem: "o1Gxr3YVvrE?t=33",
				  solution: "tcV7VN3l3bY?t=32" }
			  ]
		}
		]
}

